Hello friends, Namaskar friends, in today's
video we are going to tell you that
at our centre, helmets were distributed by ICC
because
we had done a good job, following that,
ICICI Lombard has
distributed its Ramesh at our centre,
see here the stock of chandeliers
came near us, there is one laptop at ICICI, where I am
telling you openly and after that
I will show you some pictures which were distributed at our centre, so
go and see them in the video, if you like then
like and share, it will
work well and you may be the next
seriously, at whose centre these elements will be
distributed
[Music]
You can see what a great helmet it is,
it has a lot of branding, the
color is very fine, the material is very good, the
garlic flesh was of medium size, it was
horrific, what kind of branding
is it, I advised, we will keep our promise and it is a very
good
helmet of around 1250, because if
you distribute this to your customers, then
you will get a certain status there
[Music]
[applause]
[music]
Hello
friends, I am
Ki A, do Ki A
[music]
Ki A
Today
we two